### Contact

rahul.agrawal.agrawal336@gm ail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rahulagrawal-157858139 (LinkedIn)

## Top Skills

Machine Learning
Python (Programming Language)
C (Programming Language)

### Certifications

Python for Data Science and Machine Learning Bootcamp

**Data Processing Specialist** 

**Data Science Foundation** 

Certification of C2090-930 IBM SPSS MODELER VERSION 18(V3)

Deep Learning A-Z

# Rahul Agrawal

Data Scientist Enthusiast | Python Programmer Bengaluru Nagara district

# Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Computer Vision, C (Programming Language), Python (Programming Language), Machine Learning, and Artificial Intelligence (AI). Strong engineering professional with a Bachelor of Engineering - BE focused in Engineering from DAYANANDA SAGAR ACADEMY OF TECHNOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT, BANGALORE.

## Experience

Sai industries
Data Scientist
October 2019 - Present (11 months)

#### DIATOZ

Machine Learning Engineer July 2019 - September 2019 (3 months)

Bengaluru, Karnataka, India

## Education

DAYANANDA SAGAR ACADEMY OF TECHNOLOGY AND MANAGEMENT, BANGALORE

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Engineering · (2015 - 2019)